Episode 2
에피소드 2
Kian.
키안.
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
Do not worry. I'm OK.
걱정하지 마세요. 저는 괜찮아요.
If so, great.
그렇다면 좋습니다.
Monarch
군주
I think someone is trapped, ma'am...
아무래도 누군가가 갇힌 것 같습니다 부인...
To make him drown.
그를 물에 빠지게 만들려고.
Yellen will find you soon...
옐런이 곧 당신을 찾을 거예요...
Unless I stop him.
내가 그를 막지 않으면.
It seems like he really doesn't believe me, does he ?
그 사람은 정말 내 말을 믿지 않는 것 같죠?
Tuan...
투안...
Assistant Hua who forced me...
나를 강요한 Hua 조수..
Please share this news confidentially.
이 소식을 비밀리에 전해주세요.
That person threatened my family...
그 사람이 우리 가족을 협박했어요..
So I'm afraid to say no.
그래서 거절하기가 두렵습니다.
Because of my loyalty to you ...
당신을 향한 나의 충성심 때문에 ...
I can't sleep or eat.
잠도 못 자고 밥도 못 먹거든요.
After listening to Mu Yao's advice...
무야오의 조언을 듣고...
I'm here to apologize.
사과하러 왔습니다.
I'm so sorry ...
정말 미안 하니까 ...
I hope you don't sell me out.
당신이 나를 팔지 않기를 바랍니다.
Any relationship Blood has no meaning.
어떤 관계 피는 아무 의미가 없습니다.
They just want the benefits...
그들은 단지 혜택을 원할 뿐입니다...
Avoid danger
위험을 피하세요.
Now I have been given another chance
이제 나에게 또 다른 기회가 주어졌습니다 ...
I can avoid this danger Previously hidden
나는 이 위험을 피할 수 있다 이전에 숨겨졌던
ma'am...
부인...
You can't blame me for feeling that way...
그렇게 느꼈다고 나를 비난할 수는 없습니다 ...
Based on what happened under your supervision.
당신의 감독하에 일어난 일을 바탕으로 .
A heartless man.
무정한 남자.
You only care about your wife more than me .
당신은 나보다 당신의 아내에게만 관심이 있습니다 .
what's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
Grandma, did I miss something?
할머니, 제가 놓친 게 있나요?
that's right.
맞아요.
After your senior gets married...
선배가 결혼하고 나면..
He is only interested in his wife.
그는 아내에게만 관심이 있습니다.
Now he started blaming his mother, an old woman.
이제 그는 노파인 그의 어머니를 비난하기 시작했습니다 .
Senior, I don’t think that’s right.
선배, 제 생각에는 그게 안 맞는 것 같아요.
Kian!
키안!
Come on, come here.
어서, 이리로 오세요.
My father gave me this as a wedding gift...
아버지께서 결혼선물로 이걸 주셨는데...
Now I want you to take it.
이제 나는 당신이 그것을 가져가기를 바랍니다.
I can't accept it.
나는 받아들일 수 없다.
You are a smart girl...
당신은 똑똑한 소녀입니다 ...
So you know what to do.
그래서 당신은 무엇을 해야할지 알 수 있습니다.
Because I gave you a gift ...
내가 너한테 선물을 줬으니까 ...
Just take it.
그냥 가져가세요.
Monarch...
군주...
I really want my mom to take me...
엄마가 꼭 데려가길 바라는데...
So just take it.
그러니 그냥 가져가야지.
Thank you, my lord.
감사합니다, 영주님.
Even after several years, I didn't even think about it...
몇년이 지나도 생각도 못했는데 ...
There are things that still remain a mystery to me.
아직도 나에게 미스터리로 남아 있는 것들이 있습니다 .
See you sir and madam ...
선생님과 부인을 뵙겠습니다 ...
We love each other.
서로 사랑합니다.
Surely...
틀림없이...
They have known each other since childhood ...
그들은 어릴 때부터 서로를 알고 있습니다 ...
And they are destined for each other.
그리고 그들은 서로를 향한 운명을 가지고 있습니다.
Why is he so lucky?
그는 왜 그렇게 운이 좋나요?
What are you talking about?
무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
How much...
얼마나 많이...
We are here.
우리는 여기에 있습니다.
Taman Shinju
타만 신주
Selama Ini...
셀라마 이니...
My safety I'm worried.
내 안전 걱정입니다.
화맨...
화맨...
Acts that make others suspicious of him
다른 사람들이 그를 의심하게 만드는 행위
If I don't want history to repeat itself...
내가 원하지 않는 경우 역사가 반복되는 것을...
You must start with the cause of every problem ...
모든 문제의 원인부터 시작해야 합니다 ...
He is my father.
그분은 제 아버지이십니다.
You made your aunt very happy today.
당신은 오늘 이모를 매우 행복하게 만들었습니다.
I've never seen him treat you so well .
나는 그가 당신에게 잘 대해주는 것을 본 적이 없습니다 .
Does this mean he doesn't like me?
그 사람이 날 좋아하지 않는다는 뜻인가요?
Girl, I don't like talking a lot ...
아가씨, 저는 말을 많이 하는 걸 안 좋아해요 ...
So that person might seem cold...
그래서 그 사람이 추워 보일 수도 있겠네요...
But that's not true.
하지만 그것은 사실이 아닙니다.
Princess, just be nice to me ...
공주님 그냥 나한테 잘 대해줘...
because of you
당신 때문에
That's not true.
그건 사실이 아니야.
You are kind and gentle...
당신은 친절하고 온화합니다 ...
Other people will know too...
다른 사람들도 알겠지...
Once they get to know you better .
그들이 당신을 더 잘 알게 되면 .
Jong Kediaman
종 케디아만
Bansha, open my bun.
반샤야, 내 롤빵 좀 열어봐라.
My throat hurts after just one day.
하루만 지나면 목이 아프네요 .
- Yes - Bansha.
- 응 - 반샤.
Now don't open the bread.
이제 빵을 열지 마세요.
ladies and gentlemen...
신사숙녀 여러분...
I didn't eat...
안 먹었어...
I've been out all day since then.
그 이후로 하루 종일 밖에 있었어.
I prepared tonic soup...
토닉스프를 준비했어요..
To keep warm.
몸을 따뜻하게 하려고.
What did your wife say she sent you?
부인이 당신에게 무엇을 보냈다고 하던데요 ?
I think it's better not to bother him...
그 사람을 괴롭히지 않는 게 좋을 것 같아요...
Because he has a business.
그 사람은 사업이 있으니까요.
ma'am!
부인!
Why don't you understand?
왜 이해하지 못해요?
You didn't come here...
당신은 여기에 오지 않았습니다 ...
On the wedding night.
결혼식 밤에.
A day has passed...
하루가 지났다...
The person hasn't arrived yet.
그 사람은 아직 도착하지 않았어요.
If you sleep somewhere else...
다른데서 자면...
Other people will make fun of you.
다른 사람들이 당신을 놀릴 것이다.
While you are at Hua Residence...
당신이 Hua 레지던스에 있는 동안 ...
You know how to win a man's heart.
당신은 남자의 마음을 얻는 방법을 알고 있습니다.
How did you behave like this after marriage?
결혼 후에 는 어떻게 이런 행동을 했나 ?
All right. I'll send it to you.
알겠습니다. 보내겠습니다.
Go, hurry. fast!
가, 서둘러. 빠른!
Teacher, Sikmu still doesn’t want to eat.
선생님, 식무는 아직도 밥을 먹고 싶지 않아요.
If you don't believe what he said...
그 사람 이 한 말을 믿지 못한다면...
And does not want to restore the good name of his family ...
그리고 그의 가족의 좋은 이름을 회복하고 싶지 않습니다 ...
He doesn't want to involve you.
그는 당신을 참여시키고 싶지 않습니다.
So he insisted on going.
그래서 그는 가겠다고 고집했습니다.
If he doesn't want to eat, leave him alone.
그가 먹고 싶어하지 않으면 그를 놔두십시오.
Watch out for him...
그를 조심해...
And don't let him go.
그리고 그를 놓아주지 마세요.
Tuan.
투안.
Miss Mu is a wanted criminal.
Miss Mu는 수배범입니다.
It's not a good idea to keep him here.
그를 여기에 가두는 것은 좋지 않습니다.
Because he offered to go...
그 사람이 가겠다고 제의했기 때문에 ...
I know what I'm doing.
나는 내가 무엇을 하고 있는지 알고 있다.
Sir, your wife is coming here.
선생님, 부인이 여기로 오고 계십니다.
Kian, why are you here?
키안, 왜 여기 있어?
Helps make nutritious tonic soup .
영양가득한 토닉수프를 만드는데 도움을 줍니다 .
You must drink.
당신은 마셔야합니다.
Don't get tired from work.
일 때문에 지치지 마세요 .
Thank you for your consideration.
당신의 배려에 감사합니다.
I received an additional assignment today .
오늘은 추가 과제를 받았습니다 .
So I think I will be busy for a while .
그래서 당분간 은 바쁠 것 같아요 .
It's okay, I won't bother you...
괜찮아, 귀찮게 하지 않을게...
If you are busy
바쁘다면
Kian...
키안...
I didn't tell you to go.
나는 당신에게 가라고 말하지 않았습니다.
I just came to give you some soup.
나는 단지 당신에게 수프를 주려고 왔습니다.
Don't stay up late at night.
밤늦게까지 깨어있지 마세요.
I want to go back to my room.
나는 내 방으로 돌아가고 싶다.
Come this way.
이리 오세요.
Tuan.
투안.
Please call Jidong here.
여기로 지동을 불러주세요.
of.
의.
ma'am...
부인...
Why is he suddenly cold toward you?
왜 갑자기 당신 을 향해 차가워지나요?
Because of love...
사랑 때문에...
It will completely change a person.
사람을 완전히 바꿀 것입니다 .
Now I have been given a second chance.
이제 나에게 두 번째 기회가 주어졌다 .
So I can't waste it.
그래서 나는 그것을 낭비할 수 없습니다.
Why did you come back?
왜 돌아왔나요?
what's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
Assistant Lee.
리 보조원.
Assistant Director Ji, why are you here?
지보좌관님, 왜 여기 계세요?
I want to see my wife.
부인을 보고 싶어요.
Come this way. Permit.
이리 오세요. 허락하다.
Madam, Assistant Ji is here.
부인, 지 조수가 왔습니다.
Good luck, ma'am.
행운을 빕니다, 부인.
How can we help you...
어떻게 도와 드릴까요...
Late tonight, Aide Ji?
오늘 늦은 밤, 지 보좌관?
I'm here to deliver...
배달하러 왔어요...
Family and lejar tokens.
가족 및 lejar 토큰.
I know it's well managed, but...
잘 관리되고 있는 건 알겠는데...
Because you handle it.
왜냐하면 당신이 그것을 처리하기 때문입니다.
I'm in no hurry...
난 서두르지 않아...
To manage it.
그것을 관리하기 위해.
This is your command.
이것은 당신의 명령입니다.
don't worry...
걱정 하지마...
Let me help you, ma'am...
제가 도와드릴께요 부인...
if you don't understand
당신이 이해하지 못한다면
Let me ask myself first.
먼저 나 자신에게 물어보겠습니다.
I leave this job to you.
이 일은 당신에게 맡깁니다.
You are my nursing mother...
당신은 내 간호 어머니입니다 ...
I can definitely trust you.
나는 당신을 확실히 믿을 수 있습니다.
You have to learn how.
방법을 배워야 합니다.
Not now.
지금은 아닙니다.
Madam, take a look.
부인, 좀 보세요.
This is a gift registration for home visits.
가정방문을 위한 선물등록입니다 .
Because of these things...
이런 것들 때문에...
You can do what you see fit.
당신은 당신이 적절하다고 생각하는 것을 할 수 있습니다 .
Why is he acting strange today ?
그 사람 오늘 왜 이상하게 행동하는 걸까요 ?
Maybe he's tired.
어쩌면 그는 피곤할 수도 있습니다.
How much.
얼마나 많이.
It's time to eat.
먹을 시간입니다.
How much...
얼마나 많이...
The bodyguard reports...
경호원이 보고합니다...
Mr. Mu ran away.
뮤 씨가 도망쳤어요.
If it's busy, you should go.
바쁘면 가봐야 해.
I can go home alone.
나 혼자 집에 갈 수 있어요.
We'll be waiting for you at Hua Residence.
Hua Residence에서 기다리겠습니다.
Unable to.
할 수 없습니다.
How can I leave you alone?
어떻게 당신을 내버려 둘 수 있습니까?
don't worry.
걱정 하지마.
You are good to go.
당신은 갈 수 있습니다.
sorry. Stop the carriage.
죄송합니다. 마차를 멈추세요.
road name.
도로.
Before He left me
이전에는 그 사람이 나를 떠났어요
This time I told them to leave.
이번에는 떠나라고 했어요.
I hope this will make him forgive me...
이로 인해 그가 나를 용서하게 되기를 바랍니다 ...
When you express your feelings later Later
나중에 감정을 표현할 때 나중에.
What does this smell like?
이건 무슨 냄새야?
the poor!
거지!
There is no escape this time.
이번에는 도망칠 수 없습니다.
I am good enough to offer you a job...
나는 당신에게 일자리를 제안할 만큼 좋은 사람입니다 ...
But you don't thank me...
그런데 넌 나한테 고마워하지 않잖아...
You even stole my money bag.
넌 심지어 내 돈가방까지 훔쳤어.
How will you compensate?
어떻게 보상을 하시겠습니까?
Let me know!
알려줘요!
- the poor! - It won't run!
- 거지! - 실행되지 않습니다!
Watch my stuff!
내 물건을 조심하세요!
Stop him!
그를 막아라!
- Sir... - Run away if you can!
- 선생님... - 가능하다면 도망가세요!
Do you want to run or not?
달리고 싶나요, 말까요?
Did you order food?
음식을 주문하셨나요?
Yes, I told the person in charge...
네, 담당직원에게 말했어요 ...
We will send your food when it is ready.
음식이 준비되면 보내드립니다 .
good.
좋은.
If you want to buy food...
음식을 사고 싶다면..
Just tell them to buy it.
구매하라고 말씀하시면 됩니다.
Why do you choose to do it yourself?
왜 스스로 하기로 선택합니까?
Here's dessert...
여기 디저트...
It's one of my mom's favorite things...
엄마가 제일 좋아하는 것 중 하나야...
So I guess I'll have to buy it myself.
그러니 내가 직접 사야겠어.
After all, the Zhong family store is right around the corner...
결국, 종 가족 가게가 바로 모퉁이에 있습니다 ...
So I can...
그래서 난 할 수 있어...
Look at the condition of the workers...
노동자 상태 좀 보세요..
Where did this beggar come from?
이 거지는 어디서 왔나요?
How dare you block our cart?
어떻게 감히 우리 카트를 막습니까?
the poor!
거지!
This is...
이 거지...
Steal my money bag...
내 돈가방을 훔쳐...
So he ran away and met you.
그래서 그 사람은 도망가다가 당신을 만났어요 .
I will take him.
나는 그를 데려갈 것이다.
So take him from us.
그렇게 하여 그를 우리에게서 데려가십시오.
Don't bring bad luck to our cart.
우리 카트에 불운을 가져오지 마십시오 .
Okay, let's go first.
좋아, 먼저 가자.
Qianzhi, you can't do this...
Qianzhi, 이러면 안 돼요...
Call someone a beggar.
누군가를 거지라고 부르세요.
Madam, why did you get off the cart?
부인, 왜 카트에서 내리 셨나요 ?
I can do it.
내가 할 수 있어요.
Don't let your subordinates dirty your eyes .
부하직원이 당신의 눈을 더럽히게 두지 마십시오 .
Also, if you hear someone called a beggar...
또 누군가를 거지라고 부르는 걸 들으면 ...
I will pay a fine of one month's salary.
한 달치 월급 벌금을 내겠습니다 .
You said he stole your money, right?
그 사람이 당신 돈을 훔쳤다고 했죠?
Madam, I am here on business.
부인, 저는 사업차 왔습니다.
While taking a walk yesterday ...
어제 산책하다가..
This beggar bumped into me...
이 거지가 나한테 부딪혔어...
And he stole my money bag.
그리고 내 돈가방을 훔쳤어요.
So did you find the money bag?
그럼 돈가방은 찾았나요?
Not yet. That person stole it yesterday...
아직 아님. 그 사람 어제 훔쳤는데...
And he has to hide it.
그리고 그는 그것을 숨겨야 합니다.
I just checked on him...
방금 그 사람을 확인해 봤는데...
And he didn't have a penny.
그리고 그 사람은 한 푼도 없었어요.
So I can't find my money bag...
그래서 돈가방을 찾을 수가 없군요...
About that, right?
그에 대해, 그렇지?
Beggars like him...
그와 같은 거지들...
It's a scam.
사기입니다.
He won't tell me where he hid my wallet...
그 사람은 내 지갑을 어디에 숨겼는지 말해주지 않을 거야 ...
It doesn't fit.
맞지 않고.
Did you steal his money bag?
그 사람 돈가방을 훔쳤나요?
I'm sure he'll deny it.
나는 그가 그것을 부인할 것이라고 확신합니다.
me...
나...
I didn't steal.
나는 훔치지 않았습니다.
It's no use, don't cheat...
소용없어, 속이지 마...
diameter
직경
I couldn't even find my wallet...
지갑도 못찾고...
Or catch him stealing.
아니면 그 사람이 훔치는 걸 잡아요.
You hit him...
당신이 그 사람을 때렸어요...
Without any evidence.
증거도 없이.
How can we trust you ?
우리가 당신을 어떻게 믿을 수 있나요?
If you insist...
당신이 주장하는 경우...
This man stole your money bag...
이 남자가 네 돈가방을 훔쳤어...
Report to Magistrate Don.
돈 치안판사에게 보고하세요.
But if you can't prove he did it ...
하지만 그가 그런 짓을 했다는 것을 증명할 수 없다면 ...
You may be punished...
처벌받을 수도 있다...
More than that...
그 이상으로...
Compensation for his treatment .
그의 치료 에 대한 보상 .
N.Jang...
엔.장...
You are here to do business.
당신은 사업을 하기 위해 여기에 왔습니다 .
It is better not to offend the authorities.
당국을 화나게하지 않는 것이 좋습니다 .
now. take it.
지금. 가져.
let's go.
갑시다.
What is your name?
이름이 뭐에요?
Long...Zhou...
롱...저우...
Your last name is Zhou, right?
당신 성은 저우죠?
The money he gave me...
그 사람이 준 돈은..
It will be enough to clean it yourself...
스스로 청소하기에 충분할 것입니다 ...
And eat well.
그리고 잘 먹어요.
Because there are a lot of people watching ...
보는 사람이 많아서 ..
It is not good to give money.
돈을 주면 좋지 않습니다.
You may be young , but you seem strong.
당신은 어리 지만 강한 것 같아요.
You can find a job that can support you .
자신을 부양할 수 있는 일자리를 찾을 수 있습니다 .
Come to Zhong Residence.
종 레지던스(Zhong Residence)로 오세요.
I can offer you a job.
나는 당신에게 일자리를 제안할 수 있습니다.
Nan pung!
난펑!
Bawa En. Zhou ke clinic.
Bawa En. Zhou ke 클리닉.
If you meet a troublemaker along the way...
도중에 말썽꾼을 만나면 ...
Send it to the Financial Supervisory Service...
금감원에 보내세요 ...
For severe punishment.
엄중한 처벌을 위해.
go!
가다!
Now, wake up.
자, 일어나세요.
Madam, why are you doing that in a public place?
부인, 공공장소에서 왜 그러세요 ?
In the end , you can't finish it...
결국 마무리를 못하시네요...
All these fucking problems.
이 모든 거지 같은 문제.
In the past, my wife didn't interfere.
예전에는 부인이 간섭하지 않았어요.
Do something nice in return.
그 대가로 좋은 일을 하십시오.
So, if I have a problem...
그러니까 나한테 문제가 생기면...
Maybe someone else will help me too.
어쩌면 다른 사람 도 나를 도울 것입니다.
what?
무엇?
naught.
아무것도 아님.
I shouldn't be afraid to do good things in public.
나는 공개적으로 좋은 일을 하는 것을 두려워해서는 안 된다 .
Actually, I wish I did that more often.
사실 좀 더 자주 그랬으면 좋겠어요 .
number of animals.
마리.
I think why...
내 생각에는 왜...
Has that person become a different person?
그 사람 다른 사람이 된 거야?
That person might be like that...
그 사람이 그럴 수도 있겠네요...
Because he got what he wanted.
그가 원하는 것을 얻었기 때문이다.
yes?
예?
Why didn't they arrive again?
왜 그들은 다시 도착하지 않았습니까?
It will arrive soon.
곧 도착할 거예요.
Go ahead and try it.
어서 해봐요.
What do I look like?
나는 어떤 모습인가요?
- It's not here. - why?
- 여기엔 없어요. - 왜?
Other people are watching us.
다른 사람들이 우리를 지켜보고 있습니다.
nurse.
유모.
membrane.
막.
You have important business to attend to.
당신은 처리해야 할 중요한 사업이 있습니다 .
He will join me soon.
그는 곧 나와 합류할 것이다.
great.
좋아요.
That's not important.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
to...
에게...
I almost forgot my father I am short-tempered.
나는 아버지를 잊어버릴 뻔했습니다 성미가 급합니다.
But I can't...
하지만 그럴 수는 없어요...
Waste your time grieving
슬퍼하는 데 시간을 낭비하세요.
Everything is fine.
모든 것이 괜찮아.
Your brother left early this morning...
네 동생은 오늘 아침 일찍 나갔어...
When he knows you want to come.
그가 당신이오고 싶어한다는 것을 알았을 때.
I don't know what his plan is.
나는 그의 계획이 무엇인지 모른다.
You know he can easily change his mind.
그 사람이 마음을 쉽게 바꿀 수 있다는 걸 당신도 알잖아요.
Don't blame him.
그를 비난하지 마십시오.
Go ahead and try it. Let's go in.
어서 해봐요. 들어가자.
number of animals.
마리.
Of course, you are tired after a long trip.
물론 긴 여행 후에는 피곤합니다.
Mom sent a helper...
엄마가 도우미를 보냈어...
Light some incense in the tent...
텐트 안에 살짝 향을 피우고...
To calm my mind.
마음을 진정시키려고.
Relax...
긴장을 풀어 보세요...
Before my husband came.
남편이 오기 전에.
are you okay. I'm not tired yet.
괜찮아. 아직 피곤하지 않아요.
Where is your dad?
아빠는 어디 계시나요?
He is very excited...
그는 매우 흥분되어 있습니다 ...
When I hear you want to visit.
당신이 방문하고 싶다는 소식을 들었을 때 .
You left work early in the morning...
아침 일찍 퇴근하셨는데 ..
I was going to wait for you, but you arrived alone.
당신을 기다리려고 했는데 당신은 혼자 도착했어요.
Then that person might get angry.
그러면 그 사람이 화를 낼 수도 있어요.
I think he must be sulking in the reading room.
내 생각엔 그 사람이 독서실에서 삐져 있는 게 틀림없어 .
Don't worry about him.
그 사람에 대해서는 걱정하지 마세요.
He won't do anything...
그 사람은 아무것도 안 할 거야...
When Tuan Zhong arrives later.
Tuan Zhong이 나중에 도착할 때.
Anyway, why is he so busy...
그나저나 그 사람 왜 이렇게 바빠요...
Until you let me go back alone?
혼자 돌아가게 해줄 때까지 ?
Who knows.
누가 알아.
Maybe it could be a thing.
어쩌면 일이 될 수도 있습니다.
Qian, I told you...
Qian, 내가 말했지...
You are not finished with your marriage .
당신은 결혼 생활을 마치지 않았습니다 .
Don't be satisfied...
만족하지 마세요...
Because you are married now .
당신이 지금 결혼했기 때문에 .
Life in a species residence...
종 거주지에서의 생활 ...
It can be very complicated.
매우 복잡할 수 있습니다.
Maybe they're married now...
이제 결혼 했을 수도 있겠네요 ...
But many women will still try...
하지만 많은 여성들이 여전히 노력할 것입니다 ...
To enter Zhong Residence
종 레지던스(Zhong Residence)에 들어가려면
I know what I'm doing.
나는 내가 무엇을 하고 있는지 알고 있다.
great.
좋아요.
You just got married...
방금 결혼하셨군요...
So mom, I understand...
그러니까 엄마는 이해해...
I don't care what my mom says.
엄마 말은 신경 안 쓴다고.
Although Mr. Jong...
비록 종 씨는...
I'm just a follower of my previous master...
그냥 전 주인의 추종자일 뿐인데...
Don't forget...
잊지 말아야 해...
He had...
그가 가지고 있던...
Open every store in the South yourself.
남부의 모든 상점을 직접 열어보세요.
Similar to the previous master.
이전 마스터 와 비슷합니다 .
Listen to your mom.
엄마 말을 들어보세요.
I should try to have a boy ...
남자아이 를 낳도록 노력해야지 ...
To strengthen your position.
당신의 입지를 강화하기 위해.
Only then can you help us.
그래야만 우리를 도울 수 있습니다.
Your brother isn't married.
네 동생은 결혼하지 않았어..
Our family depends on you.
우리 가족은 당신에게 달려있습니다.
I understand.
이해합니다.
Can't wait any longer?
더 이상 기다릴 수 없나요?
Only mom wants to tell you.
엄마만이 당신에게 말해주고 싶어해요.
But you don't care...
하지만 당신은 상관하지 않습니다 ...
In my mother's words.
엄마의 말로.
Mom and Dad want it...
엄마아빠가 원하는데...
I'm still worried about you...
아직도 네가 걱정돼...
After we die?
우리 죽은 후에?
It suddenly occurred to me...
갑자기 생각났는데...
I have something to tell my dad.
아빠한테 할 말이 있어요.
I think we'd better find him.
그를 찾는 게 좋을 것 같아요.
I'm not finished talking yet.
아직 말 안 끝났어요.
What do you want to say to your father?
아버지께 하고 싶은 말은 무엇인가요 ?
much.
중요한 것.
you...
너...
this child...
이 아이...
ma'am. Whoa, don't worry too much.
부인. 후아, 너무 걱정하지 마세요.
Sir, thank you very much.
선생님, 정말 감사드립니다.
How can you not worry?
어떻게 걱정하지 않을 수 있습니까?
He was spoiled from childhood.
그는 어린 시절부터 버릇이 없었습니다.
- Life here is very simple. - great.
- 이곳에서의 생활은 아주 간단합니다. - 좋아요.
He has never experienced a loss.
그는 손실을 경험한 적이 없습니다.
So he doesn't realize how complicated life is .
그래서 그는 인생이 얼마나 복잡한지 깨닫지 못합니다 .
You are smart.
당신은 똑똑.
Don't worry about him.
그 사람에 대해서는 걱정하지 마세요.
In the end, I will take care of him.
결국 내가 그를 돌볼 것이다.
Please let me know...
알려줘요...
How did Tuan Zhong treat him?
Tuan Zhong은 그를 어떻게 대했습니까?
My jealousy is...
나의 질투심은...
My father took the opportunity...
아버지가 기회를 잡게 된 것은...
To destroy your family.
당신의 가족을 무너뜨리기 위해.
So only I can change that behavior
그래서 나만 그 행동을 변경할 수 있습니다.
You have to try.
노력해야 합니다.
nurse.
유모.
What I heard...
내가 들은 얘기는...
What is Mu Yunping’s banishment sentence?
무윤핑의 추방형은?
what's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
I heard he thinks he's right...
그 사람이 자기가 옳다고 생각한다고 들었는데 ...
Stubborn and inflexible.
완고하고 융통성이 없다.
After being humiliated like that...
그렇게 굴욕을 당하고 나면..
He may not live long in prison.
그는 감옥에서 오래 살지 못할 수도 있습니다.
Isn’t it great?
정말 좋지 않나요?
Your father doesn't have to struggle to deal with him.
아버지가 그를 다루 느라 애쓰실 필요가 없습니다 .
I guess I'll have to try a different approach.
다른 접근 방식 을 시도해야 할 것 같습니다 .
My teacher and I recently visited Zhong Park.
선생님과 저는 최근에 종박(Zhong Park)을 방문했습니다.
I saw my cousin there...
거기서 내 사촌을 봤어...
And find something interesting.
그리고 흥미로운 것을 찾아보세요.
Want to know more?
더 알고 싶나요?
What did he say?
그는 무엇을 말 했는가?
so...
그래서...
Please tell someone to push me into the swimming pool.
누군가에게 나를 수영장으로 밀어 넣으라고 말해주세요.
what?
무엇?
Now I am Mr. Jong's wife...
이제 저는 종 선생의 아내입니다...
So that person holds a grudge against me...
그래서 그 사람이 나한테 원한을 품고 있구나...
And you want me to suffer.
그리고 내가 고통 받기를 원합니다.
Kian.
키안.
Dad takes care of him.
아빠가 그를 돌봐줍니다.
Why does that person want to betray you?
그 사람은 왜 당신을 배신하고 싶어하는 걸까요?
Dad is getting older too...
아빠도 늙어가는데...
And now I can't read people very well .
그리고 지금은 사람의 말을 잘 읽을 수 없습니다 .
He just...
그는 그냥...
selfish...
이기적인...
And my thoughts are narrow...
그리고 생각이 좁다...
But his father still took him to work.
하지만 아버지는 여전히 그를 직장에 데려갔습니다.
Anyway, he said he wanted to talk to me...
어쨌든 그 사람은 나랑 얘기하고 싶다고 하더군요...
But he was just looking for information.
하지만 그는 단지 정보를 찾고 있었을 뿐입니다.
If it weren't for my caution...
나의 경각심이 아니었다면...
I don't know...
난 모르겠어...
There is a spy in the servant's residence.
종 거주지에 스파이가 있습니다.
What you mean is...
네 말 뜻은...
He's loyal to you...
그 사람은 당신에게 충실해요...
But you tried to trick me into opening my mouth?
그런데 입을 열도록 속이려고 했다 고요?
Dad has a lot of sources of information.
아빠는 정보원이 많아요.
ask them
그들에게 묻다.
Anyway, I think Dad should stay away from that guy.
어쨌든, 내 생각에는 아빠가 그 사람을 멀리해야 할 것 같아요.
So what do you think Dad should do?
그러면 아빠는 어떻게 해야 한다고 생각하시나요?
Hwaman drowned me Drowned me...
화만은 나를 물에 빠뜨렸다 물에 빠뜨렸다...
Ask someone to eavesdrop on our conversation .
누군가에게 우리 대화를 엿듣도록 요청하세요 .
It's all true.
모두 사실입니다.
My recalculation Based on that
내 재계산 그것을 바탕으로
So the decoration of my story is...
그래서 내 이야기의 장식은...
Please wait a moment.
잠깐 기다리세요.
금욕...
금욕...
Collusion Collusion with employees
담합 직원과의 공모
It's not too late...
아직 늦지 않았습니다...
I'm trying to break off my relationship with him.
그와의 관계를 끊으려고 합니다.
He should have noticed Dad by now.
지금쯤이면 그는 아빠를 알아차렸어야 했습니다 .
So I think...
그래서 내 생각에는...
Dad shouldn't brag.
아빠는 자랑하면 안 돼요.
I have no intention of raising it...
키울 생각은 없고...
About your case.
당신의 사건에 대해.
a few days ago...
며칠 전...
i heard you say
나는 당신이 말하는 것을 들었습니다
Mu Yunping is currently imprisoned.
Mu Yunping은 현재 투옥되었습니다.
It seems like you value Mu's family...
뮤의 가족을 소중히 여기는 것 같은데 ...
So maybe he could try it...
그래서 그 사람이 시도해 볼 수도 있겠네요...
Ask the Financial Supervisory Service...
금융감독원에 물어보세요...
Forgive his crimes.
그의 범죄를 용서하십시오.
I think...
제 생각에는...
If dad decided to raise this...
아빠가 이걸 키우기로 했다면 ...
It may make it easier for you.
그것은 당신을 더 쉽게 만들 수 있습니다.
Kian...
키안...
Don’t you really hate the Mu family?
뮤가족 정말 싫지 않나요 ?
I finally got rid of those people...
드디어 그 사람들을 없앴어요...
the way you want
원하는대로
Why plead for them?
왜 그들을 위해 탄원합니까?
I hope I don't repeat the same mistake .
같은 실수를 반복하지 않기를 바랍니다 .
I heard you moved to a big mansion...
큰 저택으로 이사했다고 들었는데 ...
Recently.
최근에.
How can you find time to meet me?
나를 만날 시간을 어떻게 찾을 수 있나요 ?
Everyone is very busy.
모두가 매우 바쁩니다.
My father told me to do it...
아버지가 나에게 하라고 하셨는데...
Take care of your furniture...
가구를 관리하다...
So I came to your house...
그래서 내가 너희 집에 왔는데...
To escape from homework.
숙제에서 탈출하기 위해.
How about finding a trustworthy broker?
믿을 수 있는 브로커를 찾아보시는 것이 어떨까요 ?
for this?
이것을 위해?
You said I...
당신은 내가 ...
Could you introduce us to your broker ?
우리 브로커를 소개해주시 겠어요?
You can do it too.
당신도 할 수 있습니다.
I am new...
나는 신입이다...
And I don't know anyone
그리고 난 아는 사람이 아무도 없어
These tasks are very difficult for me.
이러한 작업은 나에게 매우 어렵습니다.
Don't be too formal with me.
나에게 너무 격식을 차리지 마세요.
Kian...
키안...
I'm glad for you.
당신이 있어서 기뻐요.
Do you think this is a good idea?
이것이 좋은 생각이라고 생각하시나요?
Mu Yao used me to get closer to Master.
Mu Yao는 나를 이용하여 스승님과 가까워졌습니다.
That's what I'm worried about.
그게 걱정이에요.
I recently discovered the way he looks at Mu Yao...
최근에 그가 Mu Yao를 바라보는 방식을 발견했습니다 ...
different
다른
Mu Yao's father...
무야오의 아버지...
It's been less than a year since I came here...
여기 온 지 1년도 채 안 됐는데...
But he took over...
하지만 그 사람이 인수했어요...
Jong runs a family business.
종 가족 사업 운영.
Dad can't even get close to him.
아빠는 그에게 가까이 다가갈 수도 없습니다.
I heard it too...
나도 들었어...
That person always finds fault...
그 사람은 늘 잘못을 찾아내는데...
With medicine...
약으로...
This is what my father confirmed.
아버지가 확인하신 것입니다.
He complains about his dad...
그는 아빠에 대해 불평합니다 ...
along with the entire workshop.
워크샵 전체와 함께.
If this continues...
이런 일이 계속된다면...
I'm worried about the superiors of the head family...
종가의 윗사람이 걱정되는데 ...
I will follow his instructions.
그의 지시를 따를 것이다.
Just me and Mu Yao...
나와 Mu Yao만...
Who knows about brokers.
브로커에 대해 아는 사람.
If that person tries to criticize me later...
나중에 그 사람이 나를 비난하려 한다면...
No witnesses can support him.
어떤 증인도 그를 지지할 수 없습니다.
We can help you find an incredible broker.
믿을 수 없는 브로커를 주선해 드릴 수 있어요 .
To meet him...
그를 만나러...
South of town...
마을 남쪽...
He asked me to recommend low quality furniture...
품질이 낮은 가구를 추천해달라고 하더군요 ...
This will affect the family.
이는 가족에게 영향을 미칠 것입니다.
So Mu Yao won't have time...
그래서 Mu Yao는 시간이 없을 것입니다 ...
To get closer to you...
당신과 가까워지기 위해...
And his father will be unmotivated...
그리고 그의 아버지는 동기가 없을 것입니다 ...
He competes with his father for the position of assistant.
조수 자리를 두고 아버지와 경쟁하게 된다 .
Kian.
키안.
Do you want to destroy your family forever ?
당신의 가족을 영원히 파괴하고 싶습니까 ?
What do you think, Dad?
아빠는 어떻게 생각하세요?
Finding a broker is not easy.
브로커를 찾는 것은 쉽지 않습니다.
Eventually the furniture broke...
결국 부서진 가구...
It's easy to see.
쉽게 볼 수 있습니다.
then...
그렇다면...
Your family can act on your behalf as a broker.
귀하의 가족이 브로커를 대신할 수 있습니다.
Recently...
최근에...
Perfume workshop...
향수 워크숍...
We received a large order for agarwood incense balls.
침향 향볼을 대량 주문 받았습니다 .
My father happened to see it...
아버지가 우연히 보셨는데...
Market expert.
시장 전문가.
They say it has filtering capabilities...
필터링 능력이 있다고 하는데 ...
You can make frankincense...
유향을 만들 수 있습니다 ...
The scent of agarwood is released in a short period of time.
단시간에 침향향이 납니다 .
Even scent experts can't tell the difference.
냄새 전문가도 그 차이를 구별할 수 없습니다.
impossible.
불가능한.
Why have I never...
난 왜 한번도...
Did you hear that scam?
그 사기 소리 들었어?
You don't need to know.
알 필요는 없습니다.
Agarwood does not change easily...
침향은 쉽게 변하지 않네요...
So it's heavier...
그래서 더 무거워요...
The incense hardens over time.
향은 시간이 지나면서 굳어집니다.
How dare the director...
감히 감독님이...
To deceive us...
우리를 속이려고...
Using a strong scent ...
강한 향을 사용해서 ...
How to replace agarwood?
침향을 대체하려면?
impossible.
불가능한.
I checked all the agarwood holes...
침향공을 모두 확인해 봤는데 ..
After it was created.
만들어진 후.
This is truly the best agarwood incense...
정말 최고의 침향향 입니다 ...
And it doesn't have a strong scent.
그리고 강한 향이 아닙니다.
Do you still want to deny it?
아직도 부정하고 싶나요?
I worked with the Zhong family...
나는 Zhong 가족과 함께 일했습니다 ...
For decades...
수십 년간...
I have never seen anything like this .
이런 건 본 적이 없어요 .
You know you almost broke...
너 거의 망할 뻔 했다는 거 알잖아...
What is our reputation?
우리 평판은?
Think about it.
생각해보세요.
I also worked here for decades.
나도 여기서 수십년 동안 일했어요.
How can I tell the difference...
어떻게 구분을 못하겠어요...
Agarwood and tengaras scent?
아가우드와 텐가라스 향?
I wouldn't trade it for anyone else!
나는 다른 사람과 교환하지 않습니다!
I've never done anything like that!
난 그런 짓을 한 적 없어!
Magistrate Wang, something is wrong.
왕 치안 판사님, 뭔가 잘못되었습니다.
Please give me a few days...
며칠만 시간을 주세요...
And I'll investigate...
그리고 조사할게...
Judge, I found it.
판사님, 찾았습니다.
- Bring it to me. - All right!
- 나에게 가져 와봐. - 알겠습니다!
Bring it here.
여기로 가져오세요.
Magistrate, I found this...
치안판사님, 이걸 찾았습니다…
When it breaks accidentally...
실수로 부러졌을 때..
Ferabot Mu.
페라봇 뮤.
see?
보다?
Muyunping...
무윤핑...
How do I explain it?
어떻게 설명하나요?
He said he needed more time .
시간이 더 필요하다고 하셨어요 .
Do you want to destroy evidence?
증거를 인멸하고 싶나요?
Judge Don!
돈 판사!
This agarwood powder is not mine!
이 침향가루는 내 것이 아니다!
It was found in your house...
너희 집에서 발견됐어...
And you say...
그리고 당신은 말한다 ...
You have identified the agarwood worker.
당신은 침향공을 확인했습니다.
Clearly you have changed...
분명히 당신은 변했어요...
steal...
훔치다...
Agarwood scent.
아가우드 향.
I've never done anything like this...
나 이런거 해본 적 없어...
my whole life
내 평생
I too have never been indicted.
나 역시 기소된 적이 없습니다.
Please help me explain this false accusation!
이 거짓 비난을 설명하도록 도와주세요 !
We have evidence and witnesses.
우리에게는 증거와 증인이 있습니다.
Muyunping.
무윤핑.
Whatever your appeal...
당신의 호소가 무엇이든 ...
This behavior is not tolerated!
이런 행동은 용납되지 않습니다!
I sentence...
나는 형을 선고한다...
Sell ​​your entire family as compensation...
가족 모두를 보상으로 팔아라...
To Councilor Gu and the Jong family.
구 의원 과 종 가족에게.
You have been sentenced...
당신은 형을 선고받았습니다...
Lifelong banishment from the border.
국경에서 종신 추방 .
You can spend the rest of your life there...
남은 여생을 그곳에서 보내실 수 있습니다 ...
For self-reflection!
자기 반성을 위해!
Send help! Mu Yunping committed suicide!
도움을 보내세요! 무윤핑이 자살했어요!
- Death proves my innocence - Someone...
- 죽음은 나의 결백을 증명합니다 - 누군가...
who!
누구!
I'm not trying to advocate on behalf of your family...
나는 당신의 가족을 대신하여 변호하려는 것이 아닙니다 ...
But now our family has power...
하지만 이제 우리 가족은 권력을 갖게 되었습니다...
Fearing your father is inevitable.
아버지를 두려워하는 것은 피할 수 없는 일입니다 .
Otherwise, when I was in Taman Zhong...
그렇지 않다면 제가 Taman Zhong에 있었을 때...
that day...
그 날...
They won't be very careful with me.
그들은 나에게 그다지 조심하지 않을 것이다 .
I recommend this show...
이 공연을 추천합니다...
For the happiness of our family.
우리 가족의 행복을 위해.
Our God?
우리의 맙소사?
What does it mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
at last...
결국...
My father was trained by his former teacher.
아버지는 전 스승에게 훈련을 받았다.
If you don't trust me now ...
지금 나를 믿지 못한다면 ...
He will find a new server...
그는 새로운 서버를 찾을 것입니다 ...
I am against my father.
아버지를 반대합니다.
I have a disagreement with my family...
가족들과 의견이 맞지 않아 ...
Sometimes it turns into a fight.
때로는 싸움으로 변하기도 합니다.
Now if you're a father...
이제 아버지라면...
Ask them for forgiveness...
그들에게 용서를 구하세요...
Then you will be less attentive...
그러면 당신의 주의력이 덜해질 것입니다...
And please tell others...
그리고 다른 사람들에게도 알려주세요...
The Hua family just...
Hua 가족은 단지 ...
Loyal to the Zhong family.
Zhong 가족에게 충성합니다.
Kian, you know...
키안, 알잖아...
Should hidden risks be completely eliminated?
숨겨진 위험을 완전히 제거해야 합니까?
Dad needs to know...
아빠는 알아야 해...
I hate your family.
나는 당신의 가족을 싫어합니다.
If only I had a better choice...
나에게 더 나은 선택이 있었다면...
Why did I make Dad plead for them?
내가 왜 아빠가 그들을 위해 간청하도록 했나요 ?
Hurt one person and they will all be hurt.
한 사람을 다치게 하면 그들 모두가 다치게 될 것입니다.
They don't have a chance...
그들에겐 기회가 없어...
Restore their reputation.
그들의 명성을 회복하십시오.
If you act too cruelly...
너무 잔인하게 행동하면...
People will say
사람들은 말할 것입니다.
at last...
결국...
Dad knows the real story better than I do.
아빠는 나보다 실제 이야기를 더 잘 알고 있습니다.
Qian, you are mature.
Qian, 당신은 성숙합니다.
Have you decided what to do?
무엇을 할지 결정하셨나요?
Please leave it to Dad.
아빠에게 맡겨주세요.
Kian.
키안.
Try this tea.
이 차를 마셔보세요.
Madam, why are my hands sweaty?
부인, 왜 손에 땀이 나나요?
He is actually part of the family...
그는 실제로 가족의 일원입니다...
But it's not easy to persuade...
하지만 설득이 쉽지 않네요...
People who don't die...
죽지 않는 사람들...
To become a good person
좋은 사람이 되려고
ma'am?
부인?
naught. Let's go back to my house.
아무것도 아님. 우리 집으로 돌아가자.
Huang, hurry up! follow me.
황, 서둘러! 날 따라와.
Huang, hurry up!
황, 서둘러!
fast!
빠른!
I am rude.
나는 무례하다.
I'm just looking for something...
그냥 뭔가를 찾고 있는 중이에요...
And then I hit you.
그리고 당신을 때렸습니다.
What are you looking for?
무엇을 찾고 계신가요?
Do you need my help?
내 도움이 필요합니까?
I'm looking for jade...
옥을 찾고 있어요...
My mother gave it to me before she passed away.
어머니가 돌아가시기 전에 나에게 주신 것입니다.
You are an obedient child!
당신은 순종적인 아이입니다!
What do you mean, follow me back to my room?
나를 따라 내 방으로 돌아가는 게 무슨 말이에요 ?
I will send someone to help you find it.
당신이 그것을 찾는 데 도움을 줄 사람을 보내겠습니다 .
Why has my sister become so fat?
내 동생은 왜 이렇게 뚱뚱해졌나요?
You can get as much jade as you want.
원하는 만큼 옥을 얻을 수 있습니다 .
It's a bit strange.
좀 이상해요.
Isn’t he always like this?
그 사람 늘 이런 식이지 않아?
베툴.
베툴.
I lost weight...
살이 빠졌어요...
While he was exiled For one year
그가 추방된 동안 1년 동안
He's still reckless
그는 여전히 무모합니다.
thank you!
감사합니다!
Kian!
키안!
- why? - this...
- 왜? - 이것...
I bought this brocade satin fabric a few days ago.
며칠 전에 이 브로케이드 새틴 원단을 샀어요 .
The color is white, your favorite color.
색상은 흰색, 고객님이 가장 좋아하는 색상입니다.
It was specially ordered.
특별히 주문한 것입니다.
I heard it was coming today...
오늘 온다고 들었는데 ...
So my brother spent a lot of money to buy it for you.
그래서 형이 당신을 위해 그것을 사려고 많은 돈을 썼어요 .
Make clothes with it...
그걸로 옷을 만들어...
Then your master will definitely be attracted to you.
그러면 주인님은 분명히 당신에게 매력을 느낄 것입니다.
I don't like white anymore.
나는 더 이상 흰색을 좋아하지 않습니다.
Save it for your brother's concubine.
형제의 첩을 위해 남겨 두십시오.
They don't deserve it.
그들은 그럴 자격이 없습니다.
You were born beautiful...
당신은 아름답게 태어났습니다 ...
And worthy of this precious cloth.
그리고 이 귀중한 천에 합당한 것입니다.
Praise me if you want...
원하시면 칭찬해 주세요...
But don't look down on others .
그러나 다른 사람을 얕보지 마십시오 .
That would bother me.
그건 나를 귀찮게 할 것입니다.
I'm just being honest.
난 그냥 솔직하게 말하는 거야.
Anyway, I don't like white anymore.
어쨌든 나는 더 이상 흰색을 좋아하지 않습니다.
I have another one. Don't come with me.
나는 다른 것을 가지고 있습니다. 나와 함께 가지 마세요.
sibling!
형제!
Why is my sister so mean?
내 여동생은 왜 그렇게 심술궂은가?
i know.
알아요.
Zhong Yelan must have made him angry.
종예란(Zhong Yelan)이 그를 화나게 했을 것입니다.
Why is it so cold with my little brother today?
오늘 동생이랑 왜 이렇게 추워 ?
Life is hard enough.
인생은 충분히 힘들다.
How can you love a troublemaker?
말썽꾼을 어떻게 사랑할 수 있겠는가 ..
Who's pretending to be smart?
누가 똑똑한 척 하는 거야?
Lakaman Bonus
라카만 보너스
- Let me think about it first. - good.
- 먼저 생각해 보겠습니다. - 좋은.
Tuan.
투안.
Is this the bag of money you lost?
이게 네가 잃어버린 돈가방이냐?
I saw it fall here during the day...
낮에 여기 떨어지는 걸 봤어요 ...
And you ran away before I could call you.
그리고 내가 전화하기도 전에 도망갔잖아.
Is this your shell?
이거 당신 껍니까?
Is it true what I said earlier?
아까 말한 게 사실인가요?
of.
의.
Okay, N. page.
알았어, 엔. 장.
In this case...
이 경우에는 ...
I think you did something wrong to the beggar.
아무래도 당신은 거지에게 잘못한 것 같습니다 .
What are you talking about?
무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
He pushed me and I fell...
그 사람이 나를 밀어서 내가 넘어졌어...
And I hit him.
그리고 그를 때렸습니다.
So we tied it up.
그래서 우리는 묶었습니다.
N.Jang.
엔.장.
Because you stepped on him first.
당신이 먼저 그 사람을 밟았으니까요.
Why do you talk so much?
왜 그렇게 말을 많이 하세요?
Who's the boss here?
여기 사장이 누구예요?
you.
너.
great.
좋아요.
n. Jean, I’m sorry!
엔. 장, 미안해요!
Who's the boss here?
여기 사장이 누구예요?
me...
나...
It's been a while...
오랜만이었다...
I want to hit you
때리고 싶어
Please forgive!
용서 해줘!
Waiter, another bottle of wine.
웨이터, 와인 한 병 더.
great.
좋아요.
Enjoy!
즐겨보세요.
Do you want to eat or...
먹을래 아니면...
Are you spending the night here?
여기서 밤을 보내?
I heard you are looking for an assistant.
당신이 조수를 찾고 있다고 들었습니다.
Are you here to apply?
신청하러 오셨나요?
yes. That's why I came here.
예. 그래서 내가 여기 온 거야.
I want to find a job.
나는 일자리를 찾고 싶다.